china-ogpe.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy - China-ogpe.com

This is our policy to protect your own privacy. By using this site, you may be clear with how your personal information is used and the process of our work. This policy may change without notice, so please check back periodically.

**1\. Information**

(1) Registration Information

When you register as a China-ogpe.com member, we collect all the information you enter, such as your company name, address, contact person, telephone number, fax number, email and etc. Membership statistics are derived from member’s registration information. However no specific member is named or referred to in the resultant statistical reports. Statistics are generally used to classify our members by, for example, industry and country. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested.

(2) Publishing Information

We have the right to disclose your information when we think its necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also have the rights to disclose, without notice to you, personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority.

**2\. Cookies**

(1) We may set and access cookies on your computer.

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to our cookies.

We use web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with China-ogpe.com products and services.

(2) Security Measures

All your information including account information and profile is protected. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. However, we try our best to protect your personal information. We cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**隐私策略**

1、注册信息

我们主要收集您在China-ogpe.com上注册为会员时的个人信息，包括但不限于您的姓名或名称、联系地址、联系电话、电子邮箱地址、联系人、传真，以及通过China-ogpe.com您发布的信息（包括但不限于公司、产品和商情等商业信息，您可通过登录名和密码修改以上部分内容）。收集这些信息的目的是为了执行China-ogpe.com的服务条款，为您提供我们承诺的服务，以便潜在的合作伙伴或者我们的工作人员能够及时与您取得联系，促成贸易合作机会的达成，或解决可能存在的问题。

2、Cookies

我们还收集可供China-ogpe.com及其商业伙伴参考或使用的隐含信息。此类信息包括但不限于"Cookies"、"IP地址"、浏览过的网页或其它被要求提交的信息。我们对这些信息进行收集，是为了更有针对性的为您提供有效服务。

**  **

3、 我们严格保障用户的隐私权，对用户的相关信息保密。除非用户许可或法律需要，China-ogpe.com不会泄露用户信息。
